Christina Louie

O Texas, USA

L +1 832.474.4589

☑ christinaclouie@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/christinaclouie

Bē https://www.behance.net/christinalouie

Summary

Experienced Senior Business Analyst with over 10 years of experience across the Mortgage and Oil/Gas & Energy industries.

Excellent reputation for resolving problems and improving customer satisfaction through UI/UX designs.

Skills

- User Research
- . User Flows
- User Personas
- Wireframes
- · Style Guides
- Mockups
- · Usability Testing
- Prototyping

Tools

- Figma
- . Sketch
- · Adobe XD
- Marvel

Education

- . UI Design with Frontend
 - **Development** at CareerFoundry (2019-2023)
- Management Information Systems
 at University of Houston (2007-2011)

Work Experience

HCLTech Remote, USA

Senior Business Analyst 2019-Present

Application Development & Enhancements

- Conducted design thinking sessions to develop user flows, user personas, and wireframes
- Consulted with 5-6 clients quarterly to understand existing manual daily tasks and identify pain points
- Developed relationships with 6 team leads to prioritize and plan deliverables
- Implemented dashboard views to provide metrics, reducing 80% manual reporting efforts

Black Knight, Inc.

Houston, TX, USA

Lead Systems Business Analyst

2011-2019

Product Development

- Developed 4 real estate products with complex customizations and solutions for a major banking company
- Collaborated with 2-3 product management stakeholders to understand client requirements
- Participated in product design sessions to define user personas, create user flows, wireframes, and data mappings